Jack Youkstetter

Full Stack Developer

Web developer and jack of all trades; experience with leading teams and client side interaction. A quick and coachable javascript jehova with a background in the IT industry. Passionate for literature and the arts but definitely not in a pretentious type of way, I just like to write and create stuff!

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer

Oct 2022 - Present

Vive Consulting, Remote

- Led the design, development, and deployment of Vive Consulting's agent booking platform, Vortex.
- Built with React + GraphQL + MongoDB and deployment with Heroku by Salesforce.

IT Logistics Fulfillment Team Lead

Dec 2021 - Present

Northbay Networks, Emeryville, CA

- Redesigned company website. Currently under approval by management. https://northbaywebsite.vercel.app/
- Led fulfillment team in the IT asset management department of Northbay Networks.
- Software reimaging + Hardware refurbishment

NON-PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer

Sept 2022 - Oct 2022

Lets' Frickin Game

 (MERN + apollo graphQL) Led team of 4 in building a 'looking for group' platform dedicated to finding teams for multi-player video games

Developer

July 2022 - Aug 2022

Offload

 (ExpressJS + SQL + handlebars) Worked with team of 4 in developing a marketplace app for free goods & garage sales

Lead Developer

May 2022 - June 2022

B4UBoard

 (ExpressJS + SQL + handlebars) Worked with team of 4 in developing a marketplace app for free goods & garage sales

CONTACT

- · Oakland, CA (Open to Remote)
- · +1 (510) 508-0618
- jackyoukstetter1@gmail.com
- · Portfolio: NextJs-Portfolio
- · LinkedIn: Jack Youkstetter
- · Github: JackYouk

SKILLS

Languages:

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Git + CML

Front End:

- React
- Next
- Redux
- · Css + scss

Back End:

- Node
- GraphQL (apollo)
- · NoSQL/mongoDB
- · SOL
- Express

Soft Skills:

- Team Leadership
- · Creative Direction + Design
- · Client interaction & sales

Other:

- Writing Documentation
- Docker
- QA + Jest
- · UIX Design + Figma
- Scrummastery

EDUCATION

UC Berkeley ExtensionFull Stack Bootcamp

UC Santa Barbara